[TEL]じゃ　心置きなくやれるね。
We didn't learn what happened to Uvo, but we have the chain user's name and face.
やる？　俺を？
We still don't know his abilities. All right.
[TEL]　ハハハ！
We'll be waiting in the Hotel Beitacle lobby.
[TEL]　インナーミッションで 家族は殺さないよ。
It sounds like we got the
chain user's identity.
家族はね。
He has three remaining allies. Let's go.
チッ。
What do we do? There isn't any point in
capturing Pakunoda now.
どいつも　こいつも 寄ってたかって！
If I were Kurapika, I would switch targets.
上等だ　返り討ちにしてやるよ。
If I wanted to crush the Troupe, I would target the boss. Melody's listening in on the conversation, so they should know where we're going.
それを護衛する　ゴトーら 執事達の前に現れたのは イルミに協力して アルカ抹殺を狙うヒソカだった
Initiative x And x Law
部下を抑えて お披露目するだけの パワーは　あるね。
Wait here.
無傷で受け止められるほど 俺のコインは　ぬるくねえ
They're too alert... They'll be watching anyone who walks in.
奴の能力に関係あるな
I hope Kurapika and Melody
arrived before us.
ん！
Idiot! It's Hotel Beitacle!
僕のオーラはガムとゴム。
What are you looking at, eh?
両方の性質を併せ持つ。
Should I get rid of him? Ignore him. Don't look at him.
ネタバレが過ぎるな。
Eh? This ain't no show! Damn, my future's dark
後悔するなよ　エセマジシャン！
because of the failures working for me!
死人には名乗っても意味がない。
This once, I'll close my eyes
like nothing happened. One more mistake, and you'll get it good! Now listen.
能力はバラしても構わない。
Seven on the dot. You'd best be at the hotel by then!
ほざけ！
That's a message! Seven on the dot!
キャッチ。
their eyes adjust to the dark
２度目で 僕の目が慣れちゃったかな？
if the lights suddenly go out! It's time for our last song.
さっきより遅くない？
This request comes from Kicchomu-san.
ああ　だいぶ遅いよ。
Three more minutes!
ん？
Paku and the others are here. Oh?
回転に　パワー使ったからな。
What's this? You got caught again? I get it... You changed your minds and
decided to join, right?
能力解除しないと
So you screwed up again while stalking us?
自分のオーラに締め殺されるぜ。
Didn't learn your lesson, huh?
それとも 蜂の巣のほうがいいか？
But this must be fate at work. Two more minutes.
好きなほうで逝けや。
Well, let's be friends. No way. We were only following you for the reward.
「バンジーガム」　解除
I wouldn't even want to look at your faces.
よけた！
Well, boss? They've got guts, right?
あの体勢から！
Their sass reminds me of Uvo.
ん？
They know no fear.
ん！
Anyway, describe the chain user for us.
速い！　追い切れねえ！
Check these kids again. Okay, what do you want to know?
いつでも　僕が 発射可能な状態にしておくため。
Damn, that's a smart question. Straight to the point, and he can learn all kinds
of information from it.
さて　意地悪マジシャンの 死に神クイズ。
in this week's broadcast. One minute! We have to buy time! It's no use.
僕は君からの攻撃で
lets you draw out memories
from those you touch, right?
コインを２２枚　もらいましたが
We aren't hiding anything,
and we know no—
これから　君に渡すのは 何枚でしょう？
I'll know the truth soon enough. Shut up.
ゴムの力で コインを飛ばし返す気か…
Even if we did know something, we could think about something else, and hide it from you!
ガム　解除 ナメるなよ！
You seem to be confused. I draw out the purest essence of human memory.
答えが２２枚より多かろうが
I'm not browsing through
the images in your mind.
全部　撃ち落としてやる！ おら！
My question will stimulate your memory, stirring up the dirt collected in its depths
答えは　お死枚。
It's impossible to deceive me. I'll see you next week.
チャンチャン。
Here it comes!
死に神クイズに 解答者は　いらない。
And they can't see us!
次の街まで　あと４０ｋｍ
I can't pull out my hand... She trapped it with her muscles! You're mine.
これなら持つな アルカ また　ちょっとピリっと来るぞ。
Once you reveal your presence,
I can sense you.
うん　平気。
Using the dark was meaningless.
「カンムル」！
Killua!
「電光石火」！
Give up.
ほぉほぉ…　すごい　すごい。
A pity... Well, it was a good shot.
舗装道路を あのスピードで飛ばされたら
It came from the entrance?
私一人じゃ　追い付けないねぇ。
The guy with the radio was
working with them.
[TEL]
Forget him!
We only need these two. Our eyes will adjust shortly.
アマネ　私だよ。 [TEL]　キルア様は パラスタへ向かった。
Yes. Wait, where's the boss?
カナリア　一緒に来て。
The boss is gone...
祖母のバイクなら ２人のほうが速い。
Shizuku, hold this guy for me.
ん？
We underestimated them.
これは…。 祖母よ。
Pakunoda, this is for you.
しっかり　つかまってて。
Discuss their memories, and I'll kill him.
自分で走るより　疲れると思うから 覚悟しておいて。
Hey, what's going on?
行くよ！
We missed him because he was
disguised as a receptionist!
発見！
what are you hiding?
planned out
keyword
sacrifice seconds
fragments
boss
missed him such as "blackout" and "seven o'clock."
マジかよ！ アルカ　抱えてるとはいえ 「電光石火」の全力だぞ
If these kids knew the chain user all along, why didn't my previous questioning
trigger any memories?
くっそ！ こっちなら　バイクじゃ無理だろ！
He must have been hiding his powers from his own allies!
どうする？ 先回りするよ。 どこに？
From all that, we can surmise
that he is most likely intelligent, quick on his feet, secretive,
and level headed.
キルア様の速さなら
He probably isn't bluffing.
パラスタまで １０分かからないだろう。 イルミ様は車で飛ばしても ２０分以上かかる。
He was prepared to sacrifice a few
seconds to leave this message.
この１０分差で何をする？
Which means the message must be true.
変装？ ブブ　かわいいね。
His ally can read human emotion
まぁ　なくはないかもね。
by listening to heartbeats.
キルア様が私達をまいて 最もやりたいことは？
That ally is the reason he
left this message behind.
仲間との連絡。 ピンポン！
If I talk, he'll sacrifice his own
allies and kill the boss.
それじゃ　絶対　私達にバレずに 連絡を取り合うためには？ えっと　発信機や 盗聴器の有無を確認し
But that also means that these
kids are valuable as hostages. Paku. We have a chance to rescue the boss. Paku... But...
ケータイは他人のものを使い…。
Paku!
そりゃ　基本の話だろ 今　この状況での肝を考えな！
Don't say a word. Got it?
仮に私達が　キルア様は そこにいると分かってても
Machi, focus on your threads. I'll take him for you.
近づけなければ確認しようがない そんな場所は？
Kurapika pulled it off. Since he left us a message, he'll contact us again.
あっ！ 分かったかい？
Until then, these kids are valuable hostages.
さぁ　行くよ！
I am the head, and you are the legs of the spider.
ハァ　ハァ…。 お待ちしておりました。
My orders are top priority. However, I am not your top priority.
くっそ！　やるじゃねえか。 飛行船の手配も済んでおります。
Our goal is not to keep an individual alive, but the spider. Never forget that.
あっそ。 何機？ えっ？
What should we do in this situation?
その様子じゃ　１機だな 真面目か　お前ら？
If I tell everyone the chain
user's powers and weaknesses
最低でも　５６機借りて 目的地をばらけさせなきゃ
that I learned, we can defeat him.
イルミをまけねえだろ！ さっさと手分けして 手続きしろよ！
With ease. But that will probably lead
to the boss' death.
目的地は　こっちの船 これでいい？
Uvo must have faced a similar decision.
ええ。
He died for the spider.
無人でも２名分の料金 払っておかないとバレるわよ。
Died? What did that fortune from the boss say?
これ　何て読むの？
Would it be considered betrayal to speak?
受付に聞きなさいよ！ 登録名　どうしたらいいかしら？
Or would it be considered betrayal to lie?
あんたね！ 少しは自分で考えたら？
It is the spider that must be kept alive. Right...
あっ…。 キルア様は？
I'm thinking too hard. Paku, don't worry about it too much.
あっ！　あんた　わざと私に いろいろ言って来たんでしょ！
Hurry, Phinks!
逃がすため！
The boss has been captured!
何のことかしら？
Boss...
もう　早く！　追うわよ！
We still need you.
任せるわ。 はぁ？
Even if it means
飛行船が飛行船　追ってたら そっちのほうが目立つでしょ！
It's okay.
そんなこと　しないわよ。
A number of the enemies were injured.
おとりにもなるし ゴトーと合流して動くのには
They won't move until reinforcements arrive.
恐らく　飛行船のほうが 都合がいいだけ。
What are you looking at? Nothing. I didn't expect the chain user to be a woman.
何よ！ 素のあなた　かわいいわね。
You shouldn't let appearances deceive you. Anyway, you should watch what you say.
キルア様も　そっちのほうが 好きだと思うわよ。
Since it may be the last
thing out of your mouth.
ば…　ばかにしてんでしょ!?
You won't kill me.
全然。
You left your precious friends behind.
本心よ。
I'm not so composed that
I will ignore your taunts!
[TEL]
isn't significant enough to matter. You bastard! Kurapika!
ゴトー…
If you kill him, I'll kick your ass!
[TEL]
Do you need further explanation? I consider this situation
もしもし　俺　キルア
the same as an afternoon coffee break.
[TEL]　おう　どうした。 [TEL]　心配したぞ ゴトーさんと連絡　取れなくてな。
A peaceful outing.
分かった　俺からも　かけてみる。
Calm down, Kurapika! We're on equal footing now!
えっ？　兄貴が弟を？
Equal footing? You are sorely mistaken.
[TEL]　ああ。
First of all, you've made
the wrong assumption.
ゴンを元に戻せるのは アルカしかいない。
I have no value as a hostage.
でも　イルミは アルカを殺そうとしてる。
If you insist on babbling...
俺の　「お願い」が かなう代わりに
He isn't lying.
家族全員が死ぬかもしれないから。
Everything he says is true. There you go.
遅かったね。
He isn't shaken by any of this.
素直に病院の周辺で 待ち伏せしたら？
He isn't worried or frightened of death. I can hear that he's accepted death.
病院に近づくほど 暗殺失敗の確率が上がるよ。
I can hear that he walks
with death every day.
キルアの仲間が うろついているだろうからね。
How is he capable of producing such a sound? No more!
こっちが余裕を見せたら あっちに違和感　与えちゃうし。
I can't take any more of this! I don't want to listen to you or him! Melody...
８機か… どうしても人手がいるな。
He truly believes that he has
no value as a hostage.
仲間とか呼ぶの？
But the fact remains that he is the leader.
僕　人見知りなんだけど。
What are you...
いや　いないし　そんなの。
What are you people?
もったいないけど　この針　使うか。
The spider.
お。
The boss was taken in that instant. Here's the message from the chain user.
いいオーラ　発してるね。
Why didn't you go after him immediately?
これ　刺して命令すると 死ぬまで頑張ってくれるんだよ。
Machi and Paku were injured. So? He has allies who are pro Hunters.
…っていうか 頑張り過ぎて死ぬんだけど。
So? Read between the lines!
「お願い」か。
It proves we can use these kids as hostages.
そりゃ　確かに 空恐ろしい能力だな。
If we give chase and let
them escape, it's over!
差別主義者に知れたら 喜んで使いそうだ。
The boss has probably been captured by those chains that Uvo couldn't break.
イルミは地上から 飛行船をつけて来るだろう
It'll be difficult for him to escape on his own! Probably?
俺の執事が　ダミーを７機 飛ばしてくれてる
The lights went out! By the time our eyes adjusted,
the boss was gone.
基本　兄貴は仲間を使わないから 針人間を使って来るはずだ。
We weren't in any condition to move.
[TEL]　針人間？
Okay, we can assign blame later. For now, we need a plan.
死ぬまで働く戦闘兵。
Five years ago, were you the
leader when the Troupe
針から　イルミの 強力なオーラが注入されて
Are those the chains you used to kill Uvo?
刺された瞬間　廃人同様になる。
What were Uvo's last words? I don't remember. You're lying.
モラウはハンターを募って 針人間を捕獲　回収してくれ。
I have nothing to say to you. Kurapika, he's trying to provoke you! Don't fall for it! Damn...
複数の一般人を利用して
Damn!
再起不能にした 動かぬ証拠があれば…。
[TEL]　兄貴がプロのハンターでも 狩っていいんだろ？
That proves it. I'm quite surprised.
キルアが念押ししたのは
The chain user has an exploitable weakness.
「ハンター十ヶ条」　其乃四に こう　記されていたからだ
I can use this.
確か　立候補者の中に 十ヶ条改訂や
If you don't obey, I will kill
your leader immediately. First, do not follow me.
ハンター試験の見直しを 主張しているハンターいたよな。
Second, do not harm your two hostages.
[TEL]　イルミを捕まえれば
Third, put that Pakunoda woman on the phone.
そいつらの考えに同調する連中が 結構　出るんじゃないの？
Can I ask you something first? It's about the second demand.
キルア　いいのか？ 兄貴を売るんだぞ。
The two hostages put up a struggle, and we had to break a few bones.
アルカを傷つけようとする奴は 俺が許さない。
Then we're done negotiating.
兄貴だろうが　何だろうが
What is it? Sorry, I was lying.
どんなてを使ってでも
Both of them are unharmed. This is your last chance.
つぶしてやる。
Do not fool around. Put Pakunoda on the phone.
分かった。
Ow!
テラデインとブシドラは 恐らく快諾するだろう。
You are the only one allowed
to hear what I say.
喜んで手を貸すハンターも 多いはずだ。
Move away from the others.
何しろ お前が目指してる　ここは
Did you make contact with
a man named Squala?
ハンター協会本部と同じ街 目と鼻の先だからな。
Yes. Are you aware of a woman named Melody? I am. Then this will be quick.
ただ　危険な相手だってことは 全員に警告するぜ？
Listen carefully. You are forbidden from
communicating with your comrades.
ターゲットはイルミではなく 針人間の捕獲に絞れとな。
No talking, gesturing, writing,
signaling, or making eye contact. None of that is allowed.
ああ　それでいい
You must come alone to
the place I designate.
パラスタ空港の 飛行記録データにアクセスした。
If your heart rate changes even in
the slightest, I will kill the hostage.
病院を中心に半径２０ｋｍから ３０ｋｍほどの地点に 飛行船６機は着陸する。
Understood? Now give the phone to someone
besides the previous man.
キルアと執事の２機が どこに降りるかは不明。
I'm here. I'm going to meet with Pakunoda alone.
イルミも視認による 追尾しかないだろう。
The rest of you must return to your hideout. All ten Troupe members must be there.
イルミと針人間は 飛行船を見据えながら
If a single one is missing, I will kill the hostage. Understood?
陸路で追尾して来るだろう。
Yeah. Put Pakunoda back on.
複数ポイント アタックできる地点があるので
You're to come to Lingon Airport. You have until 8:00.
そこにもハンターを送り込む。
And you must come alone.
針人間の回収を 最優先に行動すること！
Don't hesitate, Pakunoda. Bring everyone.
針の確認は後でいい！ 飛行船に近づく者は全員　捕獲！
He'll put his friends before his mission. Hey, Paku!
はっ！
Wait!
では　行け！ ゴ！
Let Paku go by herself. We're returning to the hideout.
ヒソカは　ハズレを狩ってくれる？
If we disobey, he'll kill the boss! Are you an idiot?
[TEL]　ＯＫ。 忙しくなるねぇ。
If that happens, we kill the chain user. And that will be the end.
やはり　十ヶ条の四は 根本的に間違っていた。
Nobunaga, you insult the spider.
こんな輩が現れてからでは 遅いのだ。
We have to follow Pakunoda now. This is an absolute necessity!
協会員　全ての名誉が汚される！
I concur. There's no point in letting Paku go alone.
試験を もっと厳正にすべきなのですよ。
If we continue to follow his orders, the fortunes will come true.
入れる時点で 正しく　ふるいにかければ
I agree with Nobunaga.
こんな問題は生じない。
We should follow his orders for now.
来ましたね 脱会長派と呼ばれた我々３人が
I agree. For now? How long do we listen to him?
協会を牽引する時が。
Until half our limbs are gone?
皆さん　こんにちは。
Shizuku, what do you think? When there's a fight, we flip a coin.
本日は　私　テラデインと ルーペ　ブシドラの
He's broken the rules.
共同声明を行います。
But I'll side with Nobunaga.
我々３名は　よく 脱会長派と呼ばれますが
I don't want the boss to die now. I don't want Paku to die, either.
それは本意ではありません。 我々の根底に流れるハンター魂は 前会長から受け継いだものです。
I'm sure Paku feels the same way. That's why she left without a word. I don't believe this... Talking to you is pointless.
それは断言いたします。
I would love to kill you right now, but following Pakunoda comes first.
そこで　我々は その思いを受け継ぎつつ
Wait!
共に行動する同志として 前会長が過去に所属し 八面六臂をなした 伝説のハンター集団
Take one more step, and I'll cut you down.
清凛隊を 再結成することといたします！
Go ahead and try.
代表をテラデイン。 副代表をルーペ。
Troupe members aren't allowed to fight.
そして　実動部隊のおさとして
Aren't you on Nobunaga's side? That's what my heart says.
私　ブシドラが隊長を務めます。
But the rules are absolute.
そして　今回の選挙では 我々の結束を示す意味で
If we reject the rules, we reject the spider. And we also reject the boss.
代表であるテラデインに 票を投じることを
I don't want to do that. It's him.
ここで宣言いたします。
I'll take it.
我々の趣旨に 賛同していただける諸氏は
Hello— Put one of the hostages on the phone.
ぜひとも　同志　テラデインに 一票を投じていただきたい。
You little... Here.
さて　我々の主張にも かかわることですが
Are they all together? They are right now.
さる有力な筋から入手した 信ぴょう性の高い情報の中に
But they're talking about
going after Pakunoda... Watch your mouth, kid. Hello?
あるハンター会員の悪辣非道な所業を 告発するものが
You have thirty minutes to
return to your hideout.
複数　存在しました。
You can try trickery if you want,
but your leader will die.
現在　我々は このハンターを追跡中です。
I'll call again shortly. We won't be able to follow Paku now. Damn it!
賢明なる諸君！ 一致団結して　理知と良心に満ちた ハンター協会を
The boss will die if we ten aren't together?
再構築しようではありませんか！
He's pretty smart to use the
hostages as messengers.
こうして　アルカをめぐる ゾルディック家内の争いは ハンター協会会長選挙も巻き込み さらに激しさを増して行った
Kurapika's revenge has come to fruition. And his confrontation with the
Troupe has reached its final stage.